# Mohamad Alo

E: m.alo97ku@gmail.com | Cell: (980) 475-9771 | A: 3855 Sagebrush Ln, Snellville, GA 30039

## **Professional Summary**

Entry level medical professional with Chemistry and Biology educational background adept at learning the processes associated with assessing emergencies of all kinds and delivering exceptional problem-solving and decision-making processes. Current fellow in non-profit humanitarian organization with experience with social media marketing and campaigning.

## **Work History**

### Amazon Fulfillment- Slam Operator

Stone Mountain, GA

11/2020 - Present

- Mastered amazon software and functions.
- Used computers for various applications, such as inventory search and control.
- Create, maintain, and enter information into databases.
- Filed audits and product complaints
- Controlled and monitored products coming in and out of inventory.
- Ran quality audits ensuring packages and inventory were correct by amazon scales.
- Managed electronic filing systems, recording information, updating paperwork, or maintaining documents, such as attendance records, and other material.
- Completed forms in accordance with company procedures.

#### Georgia State University - SGA Executive Vice President

Dunwoody, GA 05/2019 - 11/2019

- Set realistic time bound goals to improve student quality of life and assess the faculty.
- Promote school spirit with regular events and initiatives.
- Attend university wide meetings to advocate for student concerns and discuss issues relevant to the student body.
- Meet regularly with students to allow them to voice their concerns and interests.

### Bezoria LLC - Front Of House Assistant

Atlanta, GA 09/2018 - 06/2019

- Assist customers with fulfillment of all requests. Providing answers to any questions about ingredients.
- Maintain customer safety by discussing any allergies or dietary needs.

- Helped customers complete purchases and resolved any POS system issues. Locate items and join reward programs to promote loyalty, satisfaction and sales numbers.
- Open and close store daily and ensure the working environment is clean, organized and in compliance with health code regulations.

## **Skills**

- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, and Powerpoint)
- Film Production
- Graphic Design
- Leadership
- Photography
- Multilingual: Arabic, Kurdish, Turkish, English
- Keto Menu Preparation
- BLS Certification
- Social Media Marketing

### **Education**

#### **Georgia State University**

Atlanta, GA

Class of 2022

## Bachelor of Science:

Chemistry, Concentration in Biochemistry

Clarkston, GA

Class of 2021

Associate of Science:

**Biology** 

#### **Garinger High School**

Charlotte, NC

Class of 2018

## **Leadership and Community Services**

#### **Kurdish Medical American Association**

Atlanta, GA

03/2020 - Present

Non profit, educational, and humanitarian organization that aims to provide a platform for medical collaboration, academic advancement, community service, and mentorship.

- Successfully spearhead campaigns on social media platforms including Facebook and Instagram..
- Manage social media planning for execution of marketing strategies and community management.
- Monitor online presence of the organization's brand and engage with users.

# **Grace Village**

Clarkston, GA *08/2019 - 02/2020* 

Non-profit medical clinic offering free medical care to low income patients.

- Participated in simple clinical tasks such as taking vital signs and asking about patients history under the doctor supervision.
- Explained the proper drug usages to patients under pharmacist direct supervision.
- Shadowed primary care physician to get more knowledge about the healthcare world.
- Assisted the laboratory technician with recording patients information and organized them.

## **Mentoring Initiative for New Americans (MINA)**

Clarkston, GA *01/2019 - 02/2020* 

Formed 2018 and dedicated to helping new Americans (immigrants and refugees) enroll in college.